land-fx.com 2016-06-03

# LAND FX : Online Forex Broker - Foreign Exchange Trading - Financial Law Abiding Company

Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you. 

**YOU HAVE CHOICES**  
As a Land-FX customer, you have the opportunity to make choices about how personal information   
about you may be shared. As you consider this, we encourage you to make choices that enable us to provide you with   
quality products and services that help you meet your financial needs and objectives.

**SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
The security of personal information about you is our priority. We protect this information by maintaining physical,   
electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of   
personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the   
confidentiality of personal information they receive. 

**Land-FX Privacy Statement**  
Our Online Privacy Statement describes how we may collect, use and share information you provide when you visit this   
website, receive our emails or interact with advertisements we have on third-party websites.

We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites.   
\- What Information Do We Collect?   
\- How Do We Use the Information We Collect?  
\- How Do We Use Information From Our Advertisements on Other Websites?   
\- Can You Control Your Information That's Collected and Used Online?

1\. What Information Do We Collect?

We collect two types of online information: non-personal and personal.

**Non-Personal Information**

When you visit our site, we collect the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. In addition, we   
gather information such as what browser and which version of it you're using, the type of operating system you have,  
and which site you came from. This information helps us provide an online experience that matches your device.

When you browse our site or receive one of our emails, Land-FX and companies we work with, use cookies and/or pixel   
tags to collect information and store your online preferences. Cookies are widely used and most browsers are set up to   
accept them automatically. If you would prefer, you can choose to not accept cookies.

It's important to note that cookies and pixel tags do not capture any information that can personally identify you. The   
information they gather helps us improve your online experience and may include: 

Your response to one of our emails   
Time and duration of your visit to our site   
Pages you viewed while on our site   
We may also supplement the information we collect with information we receive from other companies. For example,   
we may use marketing segments developed by us or other companies to customize certain services to your local area   
and provide relevant Land-FX offers tailored to you.

**Personal Information**

In addition to the information described in the previous section, we may also gather personal information that you   
provide to us such as your name, address, phone number, and email. Collecting this personal information enables us to   
offer you online experiences that help you with your financial needs. For example, we collect personal information   
when you are:   
Banking online   
Applying for a new program or account   
If you've enrolled in Land-FX services, such as online bill payment, we collect personal information about your transactions,   
and how you interact with third parties such as those you pay like a utility company or phone company.   
Collecting this information enables us to provide you these services. You can refer to the terms and conditions for your   
account or service to learn how your information is collected and used.

If we have personal information from you, or information that's publicly available from other sources, we may use it in   
combination with the information that Land-FX has collected online. We can use this information to better tailor and   
personalize our service and marketing communications with you, both online and offline.

The personal information you provide online is held by the Land-FX business that maintains your account or is processing   
your application for a new product or service. You can access and/or change information in connection with your account   
or application by logging on to your account online or telephoning customer service.

2\. How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

Land-FX uses the information we collect about and from you to manage our business and to offer an enhanced,   
personalized online experience on our site and third-party websites.

The information we collect allows us to:   
\- Recognize you when you return to our site so we can personalize your experience   
\- Process applications and transactions   
\- Respond to your requests   
\- Provide you relevant product and service offers on our site and in other advertising   
Remark: Land Prime Limited has right to collect and store comprehensive financial transaction information such as Credit / Debit card information, E-wallet information, bank wire information. Above financial information can be used for further business activities of Land Prime Limited or it's subsidiary or third parties which have business relationship with Land Prime Limited without further consent.

3\. How Do We Use Information from Our Advertisements on Other Websites?

Companies we work with place and track advertisements on third-party websites.  
Like most advertisers, we place advertisements where we think they will be most relevant to customers.   
We place advertisements by developing and using our own marketing segments that may combine online and offline   
information about our current and prospective customers. In addition, we may use marketing segments provided by   
online publishers and network advertising companies.

Network advertising companies that provide these services have their own privacy policies and are not subject to our   
Online Privacy Statement. Many of these companies provide ways to avoid targeted advertising provided by, or thru,   
them.

4\. Can You Control Your Information That's Collected and Used Online?

It's important to note that the information we use about you helps us provide you with products, services and   
experiences that benefit you. You have the ability to control how your non-personal information is collected and used   
online.

**Cookies**  
You can control whether to accept cookies or not. If you decide to not accept cookies, some features and services on   
our site may not work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your Land-FX account(s).  
In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests.

If you would prefer not to accept cookies, you can: Change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie,   
which lets you choose whether or not to accept it Set your browser to automatically not accept any cookies Targeted 

**Advertising**  
If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt out of some network advertising programs that use your   
information.   
To do so please visit the NAI Opt-Out Page. Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt out),   
you will still see advertisements while you're browsing online. However the advertisements you see may be less relevant   
to you and your interests.

Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have   
compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted   
advertisements you may receive. The NAI Opt-Out Page provides a tool that identifies its member companies that have   
cookies on your browser and provides links to those companies.

**Notice of changes**  
From time to time, we may change this Online Privacy Policy. The effective date of this policy, as stated below, indicates   
the last time this policy was revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine   
whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy.

**Effective Date**  
This policy was last modified May 19th, 2016.
